{
    "id": "6215402655914d45899bdcb6e2076289",
    "title": "Compound conjunctions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f841539ef44c4b84b1e6890373014aac",
            "title": "Compound Conjunctions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The doctor ....................................... his wife attended the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as well",
                        "as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The manager .............................................. the secretary has signed the papers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "as well",
                        "as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The students began to talk ................................................... the teacher left the classroom.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as long as",
                        "as soon as",
                        "no sooner"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She started laughing ............................................. she was insane.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "if",
                        "as if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He speaks ................................................ he is rich.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "as if",
                        "as though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They talked ................................................. they were scholars.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as if",
                        "as though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He will play .................................................. he is unwell.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "even if",
                        "if",
                        "even though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I cannot admit you ....................................................... you have a ticket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "even if",
                        "even after",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They climbed up a tree ................................................. they would get a better view of the procession.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in order to",
                        "in order that",
                        "so as to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can borrow my car ............................................... you return it before midnight.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "provided that",
                        "providing that",
                        "so that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}